<idea-plugin>
  <id>com.github.zuminX.easy-swagger</id>
  <name>EasySwagger</name>
  <vendor email="1215287120@qq.com" url="https://github.com/zuminX/easy-swagger">zuminX</vendor>

  <description><![CDATA[
        Swagger Annotation Generation Tool<br>
        1.If the current class is marked with @RestController or @Controller annotation, the Controller annotation is generated. Otherwise, the Model annotation is generated;<br>
        2.You can select a class name, field name or method name to generate the specified annotation;<br>
        3.The ability to set whether to generate specified annotations and default values via the Settings-Tools-Easy Swagger page.<br>
        4.The annotation information can be obtained from the Javadoc and written to the value attribute of the Swagger annotation.<br>
    ]]></description>
  <version>1.2.0</version>

  <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <ul>
        <li> Support incremental generation (multiple annotations cannot be supported temporarily) </li>
        <li> Fix the problem that the data Type Class attribute cannot be read </li>
        <li> Fix the problem that single-line comments cannot be processed </li>
        <li> If the annotation generated by the target already exists, it will not be overwritten </li>
        <li> Fix the bug that changes the order of the attributes in the settings, but cannot be generated according to the order </li>
        <li> According to the number of method parameters, choose to generate different Swagger annotations </li>
        <li> Fix the problem that the setting item cannot be persisted </li>
        <li> Fix the problem that when the annotation has a value attribute and other attributes are not assigned and the default value is an empty string, the attribute will be ignored </li>
        <li> Prompt information and settings page internationalization </li>
      </ul>
    ]]>
  </change-notes>

  <idea-version since-build="203.*"/>

  <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.java</depends>

  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <notificationGroup id="Easy Swagger Notification Group" displayType="BALLOON" key="notification.group.name"/>

    <applicationService serviceImplementation="com.zuminX.config.SystemSetting"/>

    <applicationConfigurable parentId="tools" instance="com.zuminX.config.SystemSettingConfig" id="SystemSettingConfig"
      dynamic="true"/>

    <applicationService serviceImplementation="com.zuminX.service.Information"/>

    <projectService serviceImplementation="com.zuminX.service.Notify"/>
  </extensions>

  <actions>
    <action id="com.zuminX.actions.GeneratorSwaggerAction" class="com.zuminX.actions.GeneratorSwaggerAction"
      text="SwaggerAnnotation" description="Generate swagger annotation">
      <add-to-group group-id="GenerateGroup" anchor="first"/>
    </action>
  </actions>
</idea-plugin>